{
    "id": "73e049811c54434181444e77faf06f5b",
    "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The children were tired and slept soundly. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Here the adverb soundly describes the manner in which the children slept. ",
            "answers": [
                "were",
                "the",
                "slept",
                "soundly"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I canâ€™t see any birds or animals around. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Place words are usually adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "any",
                "or",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Ravi plays tennis every day because he wants to be healthy. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Words that indicate the time of an action are adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "plays",
                "every day",
                "because",
                "healthy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You must follow my instructions carefully. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Words that indicate the manner of the action are adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "follow",
                "my",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "You have always been a great help. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Words like always, ever and never are adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "been",
                "always",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never had an opportunity to visit a foreign country. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Words like ever, never, always, sometimes etc., are all adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "never",
                "opportunity",
                "foreign"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A cool breeze was blowing gently over the meadows. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Adverbs indicate the manner in which something is done. ",
            "answers": [
                "cool",
                "blowing",
                "gently",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The girls danced gracefully and entertained us all. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Manner adverbs indicate the manner in which something is done. ",
            "answers": [
                "danced",
                "gracefully",
                "us",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The children are playing upstairs. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "Place adverbs show where the action takes / took place. ",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "are",
                "playing",
                "upstairs"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The guests have already arrived. Which of the following words is an adverb?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "guests",
                "have",
                "already",
                "arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Let's all get together for lunch one day.",
            "description": "Time adverbs show the time of an action.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "together",
                "one day"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been raining hard since yesterday.",
            "description": "Time adverbs indicate the time of an action. ",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "hard",
                "since",
                "yesterday"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        }
    ]
}